procentive.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy | Procentive

### **Introduction**

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets out how the procentive.com website (this “Website”), operated by Procentive.com, Inc. (“us”, “we” or “our”), uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this Website. In this Privacy Policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal information.

### **What We Collect**

You can visit the public sections of this Website without identifying yourself or providing personal information. But to subscribe for the services offered through this Website, you must first register with us. When you register, we may request certain personal information, including, but not limited to, the following:

  * company name;
  * name of company contact person and job title;
  * contact information including, mailing address, telephone numbers and email address;
  * demographic information; and
  * credit/debit card information.

### **Webserver Logs**

When you visit this Website, we may track information about your visit and store that information in web server logs, which are records of the activities on this Website. The servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include:

  * your unique Internet protocol address;
  * the name of your unique Internet service provider;
  * the town/city, county/state and country from which you access this Website;
  * the kind of browser or computer you use;
  * the number of links you click within the site;
  * the date and time of your visit;
  * the web page from which you arrived to this Website;
  * the pages you viewed on this Website; and
  * certain searches/queries that you conducted via this Website.

The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer this Website, analyze its usage, protect this Website and its content from inappropriate use and improve your experience.

### **What We Do with the Information We Gather**

We require the above information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize this Website according to your interests.
  * We use your financial information to verify your qualifications for our services and to bill you for your subscription, products and services provided through this Website.
  * We may disclose information we have about you as permitted by law. For example, we may share information with regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials who have jurisdiction over us or if we are required to do so by United States or other applicable law; provide information to protect against fraud; share information with your consent; and give account information to other service providers who work for us or you.

### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.

### **How We Use Cookies**

In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, this Website and applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate this Website during your visits. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won’t have to re-enter them each time you visit.

The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don’t accept cookies.

### **Links to Other Websites**

This Website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave this Website, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### **Consent**

By using this Website, you signify your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and to the collection, use and dissemination of your personal information and data as described herein, and for the purposes described herein. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or to the collection, use and dissemination of your personal information and data, as described herein, and for the purposes described herein, you should not use this Website.

### **Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at any time, and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy simply by posting such change, update or modification on this Website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately. Your continued use of this Website following any such change, update or modification will mean you accept the change, update or modification.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you believe that any information we have for you is incorrect or incomplete please contact us at:

##### Phone: 888-264-7393

##### Mailing Address: 2321 Jack Breault Drive, Hudson, WI 54016
